Leser, Paul; Papers ger058
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Series 5 - General Correspondence, 1913-1984; 5; 16 cubic ft. 1548 file folders
  - Manowitz, Rosalyn, 1979 (Box 28 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 78)
  - Marks, M., 1923; 1926 (Box 28 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 79)
  - Martin, Ludwig, 1934 (Box 28 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 80)
  - Marx, Antonio von, 1969 (Box 28 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 81)
  - Masters, William, 1961-1966 (Box 28 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 82)
  - Mathias, James F., 1954 (Box 28 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 83)
  - Mayer, Alfred, 1945 (Box 28 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 84)
  - Mayer, Carl, 1945 (Box 28 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 85)
  - Mayer, Elisabeth, 1939-1968 (Box 28 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 86)
  - Mayer, Herbert, 1954-1979 (Box 28 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 87)
  - Mayer, Howard Andrew, 1973 (Box 28 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 88)
  - Mbatha, Mphiwa Buxton; photos, 1962-1980 (Box 28 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 89)
  - McAllester, David P., 1953-1983 (Box 28 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 90)
  - McAllester, Robert, 1951 (Box 28 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 91)
  - McArthur, Harvey K., 1953-1983 (Box 28 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 92)
  - McCarthy, E. Mae (cards), 1971-1983 (Box 28 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 93)
  - McClosky, Jessica, 1983-1984 (Box 28 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 94)
  - McCullough, Joseph B., 1974 (Box 28 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 95)
  - McDonough, Bill, 1973 (Box 28 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 96)
  - McDowell, Henry & Ruth, 1969-1970 (Box 28 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 97)
  - McElroy, Robert T., 1960 (Box 28 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 98)
  - McInnis, Raymond G., 1971 (Box 28 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 99)
  - McLean, David A., 1961 (Box 28 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 100)
  - Mead, Margaret, 1952; 1954 (Box 28 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 101)
  - Meertens, P. J., 1967 (Box 28 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 102)
  - Meier, Henry, 1945 (Box 28 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 103)
  - Mertens, Peter P., 1947 (Box 28 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 104)
  - Merton, Robert, 1961 (Box 28 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 105)
  - Mertz, Rudolf, 1952 (Box 28 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 106)
  - Metzler, Albert von, 1982-1983 (Box 28 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 107)
  - Meunier, Frank Jr., 1976-1977 (Box 28 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 108)
  - Meusel, Harry, 1953 (Box 28 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 109)
  - Meyer, Franz, 1941-1954 (Box 28 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 110)
  - Meyer, Gerald, 1945-1947; 1963 (Box 28 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 111)
  - Meyers, Allan, 1969 (Box 28 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 112)
  - Meyers, Käthe, 1971 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Meyerson, ?ke, 1938-1963 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Michael, James J., 1957 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Michail, Ronald, 1966 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Michelsen, Peter, 1954-1963 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Miedl, Josef, 1946 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Miles, John & Sara, 1967-1974 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Miles, Lyn, 1967 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Milke, Wilhelm, 1956 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Miller, Donald G., 1967 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Miller, Elmer S., 1958-1981 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Miller, Margaret D. (Jim), 1954-1970 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Miller, Margaret E., 1955-1966 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Miller, Payson, 1953 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Miller, Robert I., 1960 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Miller, Roy Andrew, 1967 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Miroglio, Abel, 1960-1961 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Misra, Bhabagrahi, 1969; 1973 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Moasosang, Pongener, 1961-1966 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Mobley, Harris, 1963-1975 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Möhren, Toni, 1964 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Moeller, Heinrich (Heino), 1934-1984 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Moeller, Helmut, 1958-1965 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 23)
  - Moffatt, E. Michael, 1965-1966 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 24)
  - Mogeen, Ella, 1948 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Mohri, Karl, 1934 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Monsma, Tim, 1979 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 27)
  - Moon, William (Bill), 1952-1959 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 28)
    See also file in Series 16, Student records/files.
  - Moor, Arthur Prichard, 1950-1951 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 29)
  - Moore, Frank L., 1951 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 30)
  - Moore, LeRoy, 1970-1973 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 31)
  - Moorrees, C. F. A., 1953 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 32)
  - Morgalla, Michael M., 1967-1968 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 33)
  - Morris, Madeline A., Undated (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 34)
  - Morris, Richard K. (Dick), 1955-1984 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 35)
  - Morton, Alasdair, 1960-1963 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 36)
  - Moser, Rupert, 1981 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 37)
  - Moskopp, Josef, 1947 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 38)
  - Mostny, Greta, 1961-1962 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 39)
  - Mount, Marshall, 1961 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 40)
  - Mühlmann, W. E., 1963; 1965 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 41)
  - Mueller, Elisabeth (Liesel), 1945-1981 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 42)
  - Müller, Emil, 1931 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 43)
  - Müller, Hermann, 1951-1984; Photos. (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 44)
  - Münster, Joachim, 1982 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 45)
  - Mullen, Mareen, 1979 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 46)
  - Mumba, Zirole, 1958-1959 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 47)
  - Murdoch, George P., 1961-1962 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 48)
  - Musoke, Michael K., 1974 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 49)
  - Nabholz-Kartaschoff, Marie-Luise, 1974 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 50)
  - Nadal, Thomas, 1948-1952 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 51)
  - Nadel, Stanley, 1980 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 52)
  - Nagle, Louise H., 1956-1963 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 53)
  - Narbeth, Gwendolyn, 1952 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 54)
  - Narr, Karl J., 1960-1966 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 55)
  - Nash, Dennison, 1961-1980 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 56)
  - Nauke, 1928; 1984 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 57)
  - Ndamse, Curnick M. C., 1958-1969 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 58)
  - Neisser, Hans, 1956 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 59)
  - Nellemann, George, 1963-1966 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 60)
  - Nessel, Ferdinand, 1932 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 61)
  - Nettelblatt, S., 1949 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 62)
  - Neugass, Dorothy (Petey), 1949-1952 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 63)
  - Neumann, Annemarie, 1971-1983 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 64)
  - Neumann, Elisabeth, 1964-1973 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 65)
  - Neumann, Gert, 1946 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 66)
  - Nichols, Ida Gray, Undated (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 67)
  - Nida, Eugene A. (American Bible Society), 1954-1966; 1974-1975 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 68)
  - Nida, Frau von, 1947 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 69)
  - Nielsen, A. W., 1973 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 70)
  - Niemeyer, Gerda, 1964 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 71)
  - Niethammer, Emil, 1952 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 72)
  - Niggemann, Hermann, 1954-1957 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 73)
  - Nitzsche, L. C. H., 1959-1960 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 74)
  - Nölting, Lilli, 1928 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 75)
  - Noether, Gottfried E., 1966 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 76)
  - Nordenstreng, Rolf, 1937 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 77)
  - Norton, Eva Joan, 1945 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 78)
  - Nose, Beverly, 1949-1955 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 79)
  - Noss, Philip, 1968 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 80)
  - Notopoulos, James A., 1954-1960 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 81)
  - Nottelmann, Willy, 1928 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 82)
  - Nurge, Ethel, 1965-1966 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 83)
  - Nyce, Raymond, 1957-1970 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 84)
    See also files in Series 16, Student records/papers.
  - Oats, Andrew, 1960-1961 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 85)
  - O'Danachair, Caoimhín, 1978-1980 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 86)
  - Oelbermann, Bernhard (Bernd), 1928-1935; 1957-1959 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 87)
  - Oelbermann, Karl, 1920-1960 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 88)
  - Oelbermann, Karl, 1961-1979 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 89)
  - Oelbermann, Robert, 1920-1934 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 90)
  - Oehler, Guido, 1958-1960 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 91)
  - Oettinger-Niebuhr, Carl, 1969 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 92)
  - Ogden, Charles J., 1947 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 93)
  - Olderogge, D. A., 1956 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 94)
  - Oliver, Charles, 1978; Undated (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 95)
  - Olmes, Jürgen, 1934 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 96)
  - Olsen, Borggaard, 1937 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 97)
  - Olson, Charles, 1954-1955; 1965 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 98)
  - Oppenheim, Adolf Leo, 1975 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 99)
  - Oppenheimer, Albert, 1927-1928 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 100)
  - Oppenheimer, Flora, 1937-1939 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 101)
  - Oppenheimer, Joel, 1953-1978 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 102)
  - Oppenheimer, Oskar (Oscar), 1921; 1932; 1975-1982 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 103)
    Oppenheimer, Katharine.
  - Osborne, Richard H., 1967 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 104)
  - Oster, Otto, 1940-1941 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 105)
  - Otto, Eduard, 1928 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 106)
  - Otto, Romano, 1958-1967 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 107)
  - Otto, Uli, 1982 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 108)
  - Parain, Charles, 1961 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 109)
  - Parker, George Gordon, 1952-1955 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 110)
  - Parker, Leona, 1955-1959 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 111)
  - Parker, Scott, 1980-1981 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 112)
  - Parkinson, Barbara, 1949-1952 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 113)
  - Parsons, John T. (Jack) & Lou Ann, 1954-1963 (Box 29 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 114)
  - Parsons, Richard, 1951-1962 (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Parsons, Robert T., 1952-1980 (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Patai, Raphael, 1955-1979 (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Paul, Bushala, 1958 (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Paul, J. Irven, 1957-1981 (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Paul, Robert S., 1978 (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Paul, Sister J. Marita, 1972-1983 (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Pauli, Hanna (Hannako; geb. Koch), 1927-1928 (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Pauli, Hanna, 1932-1933 (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Pauli, Hanna, 1936-1937 (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Pauli, Hanna, 1940-1942 (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Pauli, Hanna, 1946 (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Pauli, Hanna, 1947 January-1947 June; Photos. (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Pauli, Hanna, 1947 July-1947 December; Photos. (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Pauli, Hanna, 1948 January-1948 July; Photos. (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Pauli, Hanna, 1948 August-1948 December; Photos. (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Pauli, Hanna, 1949; Photos. (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Pauli, Hanna, 1950 (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Pauli, Hanna, 1951 (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Pauli, Hanna, 1952 (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Pauli, Hanna, 1953; Photos. (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Pauli, Hanna, 1954 (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Pauli, Hanna, 1955 (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 23)
  - Pauli, Hanna, 1956; Photos. (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 24)
  - Pauli, Hanna, 1957 (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Pauli, Hermann, 1937-1956 (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Pauli, Hermann, 1957-1958 (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 27)
  - Pauli, Hermann, 1959-1960 (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 28)
  - Pauli, Hermann, 1961-1962 (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 29)
  - Pauli, Hermann, 1963-1966 (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 30)
  - Pauli, Peter; early writings, Undated (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 31)
  - Pauli, Peter, 1947-1956; Photos. (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 32)
  - Pauli, Peter, 1957-1958 (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 33)
  - Pauli, Peter, 1959 (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 34)
  - Pauli, Peter, 1960-1961; Photos. (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 35)
  - Pauli, Peter, 1962-1964; Photos. (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 36)
  - Pauli, Peter, 1965-1967; Photos. (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 37)
  - Pauli, Peter, 1968-1973; Photos. (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 38)
  - Pauli, Peter, 1974-1978; Photos. (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 39)
  - Pauli, Peter & Sheila, 1979-1984; Photos. (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 40)
  - Payne, Francis G., 1954-1955 (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 41)
  - Peat, Carrie, 1954 (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 42)
  - Peck, H[orace] Dudley, 1950-1970; Photo. (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 43)
  - Peters, Lotte R., 1964-1981 (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 44)
  - Peters, Till J. N., 1973-1983 (Box 30 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 45)
  - Petri, Helmut, 1958-1961 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Pettit, Mary Lou, 1953-1960 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Peuckert, Will-Erich, 1958 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Pfannenstiel, Dora, 1953 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Pflanz, Kurt R., 1941-1963 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Pfleger, Wilhelm & Caroline, 1931-1962 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Philpot, William M., 1953-1962 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Piché, Ronald J., 1949-1954 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Pineau, Roger (Dept. of State), 1963 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Pitt, Malcolm, 1953; 1957 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Pittioni, R. (Univ. Wien), 1961 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Pittman, Dean, 1955 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Plant, Richard, 1976-1977 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Plenge, Johann, 1931 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Plessner, W., 1936 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Plischke, Hans, 1961-1962 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Podolák, Jan, 1966-1971 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Pohl, Robin, 1975 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Pollitzer, William S., 1980 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Pollock, J. W., 1960 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Popp, Hans & Nellie, 1982-1983 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Popp, Maria, 1964-1967 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Poppelreuter, Hans, 1981-1983; Photos. (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 23)
  - Porter, Frank W. III, 1981 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 24)
  - Postenezy, Hildegard, 1956-1957 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Power, Rose, 1979; 1982 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Präwer, Wolfgang, 1983 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 27)
  - Prahl, T., 1959 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 28)
  - Prentiss, Anne, 1955 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 29)
  - Priest, John F., 1963-1967 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 30)
  - Pringle, Lois & Jim, 1981-1982 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 31)
  - Prinz-Wechner, Josef, 1931-1932 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 32)
  - Pustilnik, Irmelin (Rena Lederfine), 1948-1980 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 33)
  - Pustilnik, Walter, 1979-1981 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 34)
  - Quelle, O., 1936; 1939 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 35)
  - Quiring, Wilmer A., 1953 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 36)
  - Rademeyer, Rowland T., 1941; 1950 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 37)
  - Raffalovich, Ada, 1951-1957 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 38)
  - Raglan, Lord, 1963 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 39)
  - Rahbar, Daud, 1961-1962 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 40)
  - Rahmann, P. Rudolf, 1955-1963 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 41)
  - Rainey, Froelich, 1955-1956 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 42)
  - Ramsey, John, 1953-1957 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 43)
  - Ramsey, Robert G., 1948-1950 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 44)
  - Ranberg, Johan, 1955 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 45)
  - Rapp, E. L., 1952 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 46)
  - Rasmussen, Holger, 1956; 1966 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 47)
  - Rauber, Ulrich, 1960-1972 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 48)
  - Raudnitz, Max, 1946 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 49)
  - Ray, H. J. (Bud), 1952 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 50)
  - Redfield, Robert, 1954 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 51)
  - Reed, Arthur L., 1963 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 52)
  - Reggio, L. Erdna, 1945-1962 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 53)
  - Reid, Gene (Cyclone), 1951-1952 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 54)
  - Reid, J. Jefferson, 1981 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 55)
  - Reif, Franz, 1945 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 56)
  - Reif, Paul, 1948-1978 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 57)
  - Reinemann, John Otto, 1972 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 58)
  - Reining, Conrad (American Anthropological Association), 1949-1976 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 59)
  - Reithmeier (Schäfer), Margot, 1944-1953 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 60)
  - Reitzenstein, Joseph (Baron), 1937 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 61)
  - Renner, Natasha, 1959 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 62)
  - Reuss, Irmelin, 1963; 1965 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 63)
  - Reuter, Alfred, 1928 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 64)
  - Reyburn, William D., 1961 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 65)
  - Reynolds, Douglas L., 1964 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 66)
  - Reynolds, Hubert & Harriet, 1952-1955 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 67)
  - Reynolds, Hubert & Harriet, 1956 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 68)
  - Reynolds, Hubert & Harriet, 1957-1958 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 69)
  - Reynolds, Hubert & Harriet, 1959-1962 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 70)
  - Reynolds, Hubert & Harriet, 1963-1964 (Box 31 (5-Series 5 - General Correspondence), Folder 71)